<resources>
    <string name="app_name">OneStop</string>
    <string name="splash_screen">Splash Screen Image</string>
    <string name="by_dhruv_nargund">By Dhruv Nargund</string>
    <string name="search">Search…</string>
    <string name="these_are_the_locations_that_you_ve_viewed_recently">These are the locations people showed most the interest in !</string>
    <string name="all_activities_in_melbourne">ALL ACTIVITIES IN MELBOURNE -></string>
    <string name="app_title">App Title</string>
    <string name="this_is_a_sample_description_for_the_location_that_is_going_to_be_featured_here_to_check_how_much_text_we_can_actually_fit_it_is_a_placeholder">This is a sample description for the location that is going to be featured here to check how much text we can actually fit. it is a placeholder</string>
    <string name="most_nviewed_nlocations">MOST\nVIEWED\nLOCATIONS</string>
    <string name="museums_and_art_galleries">MUSEUMS AND ART GALLERIES-></string>
    <string name="parks_gardens">PARKS AND GARDENS-></string>
    <string name="melbourne_travel_tips">MELBOURNE TRAVEL TIPS-></string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="already_signed_up_please_login">Already Signed up! Please login</string>
    <string name="enter_your_email">Enter your Email</string>
    <string name="enter_your_password">Enter your Password</string>
    <string name="register_here">Register here!</string>
    <string name="artvo_immersive_art_gallery">ArtVo Immersive Art Gallery</string>
    <string name="artvo_is_an_art_gallery_with_a_difference_this_immersive_art_space_encourages_people_to_touch_play_and_interact_with_the_art_and_there_are_11_themed_zones_to_explore_save_time_searching_for_cool_photo_opportunities_in_melbourne_and_benefit_from_a_place_that_has_lots_of_great_backdrops_including_angel_wings_the_canals_of_venice_and_the_taj_mahal">ArtVo is an art gallery with a difference—this immersive art space encourages people to touch, play, and interact with the art, and there are 11 themed zones to explore. Save time searching for cool photo opportunities in Melbourne, and benefit from a place that has lots of great backdrops, including angel wings, the canals of Venice, and the Taj Mahal.</string>
    <string name="australian_center_for_the_moving_image">Australian Center for the Moving Image</string>
    <string name="the_australian_centre_for_the_moving_image_acmi_at_federation_square_melbourne_is_australia_s_national_museum_of_film_video_games_digital_culture_and_art_acmi_started_life_as_the_state_film_centre_of_victoria_in_1946_during_the_2015_16_financial_year_1_45_million_people_visited_acmi_the_second_highest_attendance_of_any_gallery_or_museum_in_australia_and_the_most_visited_moving_image_museum_in_the_world_in_may_2019_acmi_closed_to_the_public_to_begin_a_40_million_redevelopment_on_1_january_2002_the_australian_centre_for_the_moving_image_was_officially_established_by_the_film_act_2001_victoria_the_first_stage_was_opened_in_october_with_two_exhibitions_deep_space_sensation_and_immersion_and_ngarinyin_pathways_dulwan_running_in_acmi_s_screen_gallery_a_few_weeks_later_acmi_cinemas_officially_opened">The Australian Centre for the Moving Image (ACMI), at Federation Square, Melbourne, is Australia\'s national museum of film, video games, digital culture and art. ACMI started life as the State Film Centre of Victoria in 1946. During the 2015–16 financial year, 1.45 million people visited ACMI, the second-highest attendance of any gallery or museum in Australia, and the most visited moving image museum in the world.In May 2019, ACMI closed to the public to begin a $40 million redevelopment. On 1 January 2002, the Australian Centre for the Moving Image was officially established by the Film Act 2001 (Victoria). The first stage was opened in October, with two exhibitions, Deep Space: Sensation and Immersion and Ngarinyin Pathways Dulwan, running in ACMI\'s Screen Gallery. A few weeks later, ACMI Cinemas officially opened.</string>
    <string name="the_ian_potter_center_ngv">The Ian Potter Center NGV</string>
    <string name="the_ian_potter_centre_ngv_australia_is_an_art_gallery_that_houses_the_australian_part_of_the_art_collection_of_the_national_gallery_of_victoria_ngv_the_ian_potter_centre_ngv_australia_is_located_at_federation_square_in_melbourne_victoria_while_the_gallery_s_international_works_are_displayed_at_the_ngv_international_on_st_kilda_road_there_are_over_20_000_australian_artworks_including_paintings_sculpture_prints_photography_fashion_and_textiles_and_the_collection_is_one_of_the_oldest_and_most_well_known_in_the_country_the_ian_potter_centre_is_a_legacy_of_the_businessman_and_philanthropist_sir_ian_potter_well_known_works_at_the_ian_potter_centre_include_frederick_mccubbin_s_the_pioneer_1904_and_tom_roberts_shearing_the_rams_1890_also_featured_are_works_from_sidney_nolan_arthur_boyd_albert_tucker_arthur_streeton_john_perceval_margaret_preston_bill_henson_howard_arkley_and_fred_williams">The Ian Potter Centre: NGV Australia is an art gallery that houses the Australian part of the art collection of the National Gallery of Victoria (NGV). The Ian Potter Centre: NGV Australia is located at Federation Square in Melbourne, Victoria; while the gallery\'s international works are displayed at the NGV International on St Kilda Road. There are over 20,000 Australian artworks, including paintings, sculpture, prints, photography, fashion and textiles, and the collection is one of the oldest and most well known in the country. The Ian Potter Centre is a legacy of the businessman and philanthropist Sir Ian Potter. Well-known works at the Ian Potter Centre include Frederick McCubbin\'s The pioneer (1904) and Tom Roberts\' Shearing the Rams (1890). Also featured are works from Sidney Nolan, Arthur Boyd, Albert Tucker, Arthur Streeton, John Perceval, Margaret Preston, Bill Henson, Howard Arkley and Fred Williams.</string>
    <string name="melbourne_museum">Melbourne Museum</string>
    <string name="melbourne_museum_is_a_natural_and_cultural_history_museum_located_in_the_carlton_gardens_in_melbourne_australia_located_adjacent_to_the_royal_exhibition_building_it_is_the_largest_museum_in_the_southern_hemisphere_the_museum_was_opened_in_2000_as_a_project_of_the_government_of_victoria_on_behalf_of_museums_victoria_who_administrates_the_venue_melbourne_museum_is_a_rich_response_to_melbourne_s_urban_condition_and_provides_a_place_for_education_history_culture_and_society_to_engage_with_each_other_in_a_contemporary_setting_it_is_now_an_important_part_of_melbourne_s_soft_infrastructure_and_is_consistently_ranked_as_one_of_the_most_popular_museums_and_tourist_attractions_in_australia_winning_best_tourist_attraction_at_the_australian_tourism_awards_in_2011">Melbourne Museum is a natural and cultural history museum located in the Carlton Gardens in Melbourne, Australia. Located adjacent to the Royal Exhibition Building, it is the largest museum in the Southern Hemisphere. The museum was opened in 2000 as a project of the Government of Victoria, on behalf of Museums Victoria who administrates the venue. Melbourne museum is a rich response to Melbourne\'s urban condition, and provides a place for education, history, culture and society to engage with each other in a contemporary setting. It is now an important part of Melbourne\'s soft infrastructure and is consistently ranked as one of the most popular museums and tourist attractions in Australia, winning \'Best Tourist Attraction\' at the Australian Tourism Awards in 2011.</string>
    <string name="national_gallery_of_victoria">National Gallery Of Victoria</string>
    <string name="the_national_gallery_of_victoria_is_an_art_gallery_and_museum_in_melbourne_australia_started_in_1861_it_is_the_oldest_and_the_largest_public_art_gallery_in_australia_the_main_gallery_is_located_in_st_kilda_road_at_southbank_with_a_branch_gallery_at_federation_square_the_st_kilda_road_gallery_designed_by_sir_roy_grounds_opened_in_1968_since_december_2003_ngv_has_operated_across_two_sites_ngv_international_on_st_kilda_road_redesigned_by_mario_bellini_and_the_ian_potter_centre_ngv_australia_at_federation_square_designed_by_lab_architecture_studio_when_the_gallery_opened_victoria_had_been_an_independent_colony_for_ten_years_after_the_victorian_gold_rush_it_was_easily_the_richest_part_of_australia_and_melbourne_the_largest_city_generous_gifts_from_rich_citizens_including_the_industrialist_alfred_felton_made_it_possible_for_the_national_gallery_to_start_buying_large_collections_of_overseas_works_from_both_old_and_modern_masters_it_has_over_65_000_works_of_art">The National Gallery of Victoria is an art gallery and museum in Melbourne, Australia. Started in 1861, it is the oldest and the largest public art gallery in Australia. The main gallery is located in St Kilda Road, at Southbank, with a branch gallery at Federation Square. The St Kilda Road Gallery, designed by Sir Roy Grounds, opened in 1968. Since December 2003, NGV has operated across two sites – NGV International on St Kilda Road, redesigned by Mario Bellini, and The Ian Potter Centre: NGV Australia at Federation Square, designed by LAB Architecture Studio. When the gallery opened, Victoria had been an independent colony for ten years. After the Victorian gold rush, it was easily the richest part of Australia, and Melbourne the largest city. Generous gifts from rich citizens, including the industrialist Alfred Felton, made it possible for the National Gallery to start buying large collections of overseas works from both old and modern masters. It has over 65,000 works of art.</string>
    <string name="national_sports_museum">National Sports Museum</string>
    <string name="the_australian_sports_museum_formerly_the_national_sports_museum_is_a_museum_dedicated_to_australian_sport_and_is_located_within_the_melbourne_cricket_ground_in_melbourne_australia_there_are_exhibits_for_sports_such_as_cricket_australian_rules_football_the_summer_and_winter_olympic_games_tennis_rugby_league_rugby_union_soccer_basketball_boxing_and_netball_the_australian_sports_hall_of_fame_is_also_located_within_the_museum_along_with_the_australian_racing_museum_and_the_melbourne_cricket_club_museum_the_adjoining_mcc_museum_features_exhibitions_relating_to_the_history_of_the_melbourne_cricket_club_on_6_october_2010_the_australian_racing_museum_was_absorbed_into_the_australian_sports_museum_which_has_now_resulted_in_horse_racing_standing_alongside_other_prominent_australian_sports">The Australian Sports Museum (formerly the National Sports Museum) is a museum dedicated to Australian sport and is located within the Melbourne Cricket Ground in Melbourne, Australia. There are exhibits for sports such as cricket, Australian rules football, the Summer and Winter Olympic Games, tennis, rugby league, rugby union, soccer, basketball, boxing and netball. The Australian Sports Hall of Fame is also located within the museum along with the Australian Racing Museum and the Melbourne Cricket Club Museum. The adjoining MCC Museum features exhibitions relating to the history of the Melbourne Cricket Club. On 6 October 2010, the Australian Racing Museum was absorbed into the Australian Sports Museum, which has now resulted in horse racing standing alongside other prominent Australian sports.</string>
    <string name="old_melbourne_gaol">Old Melbourne Gaol</string>
    <string name="the_old_melbourne_gaol_is_a_former_jail_and_current_museum_on_russell_street_in_melbourne_victoria_australia_it_consists_of_a_bluestone_building_and_courtyard_and_is_located_next_to_the_old_city_police_watch_house_and_city_courts_buildings_it_was_first_constructed_starting_in_1839_and_during_its_operation_as_a_prison_between_1845_and_1924_it_held_and_executed_some_of_australia_s_most_notorious_criminals_including_bushranger_ned_kelly_and_serial_killer_frederick_bailey_deeming_in_total_133_people_were_executed_by_hanging_though_it_was_used_briefly_during_world_war_ii_it_formally_ceased_operating_as_a_prison_in_1924_with_parts_of_the_jail_being_incorporated_into_the_rmit_university_and_the_rest_becoming_a_museum_the_three_storey_museum_displays_information_and_memorabilia_of_the_prisoners_and_staff_including_death_masks_of_the_executed_criminals">The Old Melbourne Gaol is a former jail and current museum on Russell Street, in Melbourne, Victoria, Australia. It consists of a bluestone building and courtyard, and is located next to the old City Police Watch House and City Courts buildings. It was first constructed starting in 1839, and during its operation as a prison between 1845 and 1924, it held and executed some of Australia\'s most notorious criminals, including bushranger Ned Kelly and serial killer Frederick Bailey Deeming. In total, 133 people were executed by hanging. Though it was used briefly during World War II, it formally ceased operating as a prison in 1924; with parts of the jail being incorporated into the RMIT University, and the rest becoming a museum. The three-storey museum displays information and memorabilia of the prisoners and staff, including death masks of the executed criminals.</string>
    <string name="polly_woodside">Polly Woodside</string>
    <string name="polly_woodside_is_a_belfast_built_three_masted_iron_hulled_barque_preserved_in_melbourne_victoria_australia_and_forming_the_central_feature_of_the_south_wharf_precinct_the_ship_was_originally_built_in_belfast_by_william_j_woodside_and_was_launched_in_1885_polly_woodside_is_typical_of_thousands_of_smaller_iron_barques_built_in_the_last_days_of_sail_intended_for_deep_water_trade_around_the_world_and_designed_to_be_operated_as_economically_as_possible">Polly Woodside is a Belfast-built, three-masted, iron-hulled barque, preserved in Melbourne, Victoria (Australia), and forming the central feature of the South Wharf precinct. The ship was originally built in Belfast by William J. Woodside and was launched in 1885. Polly Woodside is typical of thousands of smaller iron barques built in the last days of sail, intended for deep water trade around the world and designed to be operated as economically as possible.</string>
    <string name="royal_exhibition_building">Royal Exhibition Building</string>
    <string name="the_royal_exhibition_building_is_a_world_heritage_listed_building_in_melbourne_victoria_australia_built_in_1879_80_as_part_of_the_international_exhibition_movement_which_presented_over_50_exhibitions_between_1851_and_1915_around_the_globe_the_building_sits_on_approximately_26_hectares_64_acres_is_150_metres_490_ft_long_and_is_surrounded_by_four_city_streets_1_it_is_at_9_nicholson_street_in_the_carlton_gardens_flanked_by_victoria_carlton_and_rathdowne_streets_at_the_north_eastern_edge_of_the_central_business_district_it_was_built_to_host_the_melbourne_international_exhibition_in_1880_81_and_then_hosted_the_even_larger_centennial_international_exhibition_in_1888_and_the_formal_opening_of_the_first_parliament_of_australia_in_1901_the_building_is_representative_of_the_money_and_pride_victoria_had_in_the_1870s">The Royal Exhibition Building is a World Heritage–listed building in Melbourne, Victoria, Australia, built in 1879–80 as part of the international exhibition movement, which presented over 50 exhibitions between 1851 and 1915 around the globe. The building sits on approximately 26 hectares (64 acres), is 150 metres (490 ft) long and is surrounded by four city streets.[1] It is at 9 Nicholson Street in the Carlton Gardens, flanked by Victoria, Carlton and Rathdowne Streets, at the north-eastern edge of the central business district. It was built to host the Melbourne International Exhibition in 1880–81, and then hosted the even larger Centennial International Exhibition in 1888, and the formal opening of the first Parliament of Australia in 1901. The building is representative of the money and pride Victoria had in the 1870s.</string>
    <string name="scienceworks">Scienceworks</string>
    <string name="scienceworks_is_a_science_museum_in_melbourne_australia_it_is_a_venue_of_museums_victoria_which_administers_the_cultural_and_scientific_collections_of_the_state_of_victoria_it_is_located_in_the_suburb_of_spotswood_opened_on_28_march_1992_scienceworks_is_housed_in_a_purpose_built_building_styled_along_industrial_lines_near_the_historic_spotswood_pumping_station_constructed_in_1897_whose_steam_engines_form_an_associated_exhibit_displays_and_activities_offered_by_the_museum_include_hands_on_experiments_demonstrations_and_tours_the_lightning_room_is_a_120_seat_auditorium_that_presents_demonstrations_about_electricity_featuring_a_giant_tesla_coil_capable_of_generating_two_million_volts_of_electricity_producing_three_metre_lightning_bolts_melbourne_planetarium_is_housed_on_site">Scienceworks is a science museum in Melbourne, Australia. It is a venue of Museums Victoria which administers the cultural and scientific collections of the State of Victoria. It is located in the suburb of Spotswood. Opened on 28 March 1992, Scienceworks is housed in a purpose-built building \'styled along industrial lines\' near the historic Spotswood Pumping Station,constructed in 1897, whose steam engines form an associated exhibit. Displays and activities offered by the museum include hands-on experiments, demonstrations, and tours. The \'lightning room\' is a 120-seat auditorium that presents demonstrations about electricity, featuring a giant Tesla Coil, capable of generating two million volts of electricity, producing three metre lightning bolts. Melbourne Planetarium is housed on site.</string>
    <string name="alexandra_gardens">Alexandra Gardens</string>
    <string name="the_alexandra_gardens_are_located_on_the_south_bank_of_the_yarra_river_opposite_federation_square_and_the_melbourne_central_business_district_in_victoria_australia_the_gardens_are_bounded_by_the_yarra_river_to_the_north_princes_and_swan_street_bridges_with_queen_victoria_gardens_and_kings_domain_across_alexandra_avenue_to_the_south_the_gardens_are_part_of_the_domain_parklands_which_stretch_to_the_royal_botanic_gardens_and_were_first_laid_out_in_1901_under_the_direction_of_carlo_catani_chief_engineer_of_the_public_works_department_the_alexandra_gardens_were_named_in_honor_of_alexandra_of_denmark_in_the_year_her_reign_as_queen_consort_of_the_united_kingdom_and_the_british_dominions_and_empress_consort_of_india_began_the_alexandra_gardens_are_listed_on_the_victorian_heritage_register_due_to_their_historical_and_archaeological_significance">The Alexandra Gardens are located on the south bank of the Yarra River, opposite Federation Square and the Melbourne Central Business District, in Victoria, Australia. The Gardens are bounded by the Yarra River to the north, Princes and Swan street bridges, with Queen Victoria Gardens and Kings Domain across Alexandra Avenue to the south. The gardens are part of the Domain parklands which stretch to the Royal Botanic Gardens and were first laid out in 1901, under the direction of Carlo Catani, Chief Engineer of the Public Works Department. The Alexandra Gardens were named in honor of Alexandra of Denmark, in the year her reign as Queen Consort of the United Kingdom and the British Dominions and Empress consort of India began. The Alexandra Gardens are listed on the Victorian Heritage Register due to their historical and archaeological significance.</string>
    <string name="carlton_gardens">Carlton Gardens</string>
    <string name="the_carlton_gardens_is_a_world_heritage_site_located_on_the_northeastern_edge_of_the_central_business_district_in_the_suburb_of_carlton_in_melbourne_australia_a_popular_picnic_and_barbecue_area_the_heritage_listed_carlton_gardens_are_home_to_an_array_of_wildlife_including_brushtail_possums_the_26_hectare_64_acre_site_contains_the_royal_exhibition_building_melbourne_museum_and_imax_cinema_tennis_courts_and_an_award_winning_children_s_playground_the_rectangular_site_is_bound_by_victoria_street_rathdowne_street_carlton_street_and_nicholson_street_from_the_exhibition_building_the_gardens_gently_slope_down_to_the_southwest_and_northeast_according_to_the_world_heritage_listing_the_royal_exhibition_buildings_and_carlton_gardens_are_of_historical_architectural_aesthetic_social_and_scientific_botanical_significance_to_the_state_of_victoria">The Carlton Gardens is a World Heritage Site located on the northeastern edge of the Central Business District in the suburb of Carlton, in Melbourne, Australia. A popular picnic and barbecue area, the heritage-listed Carlton Gardens are home to an array of wildlife, including brushtail possums. The 26-hectare (64-acre) site contains the Royal Exhibition Building, Melbourne Museum and Imax Cinema, tennis courts and an award-winning children\'s playground. The rectangular site is bound by Victoria Street, Rathdowne Street, Carlton Street, and Nicholson Street. From the Exhibition building the gardens gently slope down to the southwest and northeast. According to the World Heritage listing the Royal Exhibition Buildings and Carlton Gardens are \'\'of historical, architectural, aesthetic, social and scientific (botanical) significance to the State of Victoria.\'\'</string>
    <string name="fitzroy_gardens">Fitzroy Gardens</string>
    <string name="the_fitzroy_gardens_are_26_hectares_64_acres_located_on_the_southeastern_edge_of_the_melbourne_central_business_district_in_east_melbourne_victoria_australia_the_gardens_are_bounded_by_clarendon_street_albert_street_lansdowne_street_and_wellington_parade_with_the_treasury_gardens_across_lansdowne_street_to_the_west_the_gardens_are_one_of_the_major_victorian_era_landscaped_gardens_in_australia_and_add_to_melbourne_s_claim_to_being_the_garden_city_of_australia_set_within_the_gardens_are_an_ornamental_lake_a_scarred_tree_a_visitor_information_centre_and_cafe_a_conservatory_cooks_cottage_a_house_where_the_parents_of_james_cook_lived_brought_from_england_in_the_1930s_tree_lined_avenues_a_model_tudor_village_a_band_pavilion_a_rotunda_the_fairies_tree_fountains_and_sculptures">The Fitzroy Gardens are 26 hectares (64 acres) located on the southeastern edge of the Melbourne Central Business District in East Melbourne, Victoria, Australia. The gardens are bounded by Clarendon Street, Albert Street, Lansdowne Street, and Wellington Parade with the Treasury Gardens across Lansdowne street to the west. The gardens are one of the major Victorian era landscaped gardens in Australia and add to Melbourne\'s claim to being the garden city of Australia. Set within the gardens are an ornamental lake, a scarred tree, a visitor information centre and cafe, a conservatory, Cooks\' Cottage (a house where the parents of James Cook lived, brought from England in the 1930s), tree-lined avenues, a model Tudor village, a band pavilion, a rotunda, the \'Fairies\' Tree\', fountains and sculptures.</string>
    <string name="flagstaff_gardens">Flagstaff Gardens</string>
    <string name="flagstaff_gardens_is_the_oldest_park_in_melbourne_victoria_australia_first_established_in_1862_today_it_is_one_of_the_most_visited_and_widely_used_parks_in_the_city_by_residents_nearby_office_workers_and_tourists_the_gardens_are_notable_for_their_archaeological_horticultural_historical_and_social_significance_to_the_history_of_melbourne_the_gardens_are_7_2_hectares_18_acres_of_crown_land_bounded_by_william_la_trobe_king_and_dudley_streets_managed_by_the_city_of_melbourne_on_the_southeast_corner_opposite_is_the_entrance_to_flagstaff_railway_station_diagonally_opposite_stands_the_victorian_branch_of_the_royal_mint_established_7_august_1869_the_former_royal_mint_building_is_a_well_preserved_example_of_victorian_gold_rush_boom_period_classical_styled_architecture_the_facade_features_paired_columns_with_scrolled_capitals_and_the_royal_mint_coat_of_arms">Flagstaff Gardens is the oldest park in Melbourne, Victoria, Australia, first established in 1862. Today it is one of the most visited and widely used parks in the city by residents, nearby office workers and tourists. The gardens are notable for their archaeological, horticultural, historical and social significance to the history of Melbourne. The gardens are 7.2 hectares (18 acres) of Crown Land bounded by William, La Trobe, King and Dudley streets, managed by the City of Melbourne. On the southeast corner opposite is the entrance to Flagstaff railway station. Diagonally opposite stands the Victorian branch of the Royal Mint, established 7 August 1869. The former Royal Mint building is a well-preserved example of Victorian Gold Rush boom-period classical styled architecture. The facade features paired columns with scrolled capitals and the Royal Mint coat-of-arms.</string>
    <string name="royal_botanical_gardens">Royal Botanical Gardens</string>
    <string name="royal_botanic_gardens_victoria_are_botanic_gardens_across_two_sites_melbourne_and_cranbourne_melbourne_gardens_was_founded_in_1846_when_land_was_reserved_on_the_south_side_of_the_yarra_river_for_a_new_botanic_garden_it_extends_across_38_hectares_94_acres_that_slope_to_the_river_with_trees_garden_beds_lakes_and_lawns_it_displays_almost_50_000_individual_plants_representing_8_500_different_species_these_are_displayed_in_30_living_plant_collections_royal_botanic_gardens_victoria_is_home_to_the_state_botanical_collection_which_is_housed_in_the_national_herbarium_of_victoria_the_collection_which_includes_1_5_million_preserved_plants_algae_and_fungi_represents_the_largest_herbarium_collection_in_australia_and_wider_oceania_it_also_includes_australia_s_most_comprehensive_botanical_library">Royal Botanic Gardens Victoria are botanic gardens across two sites - Melbourne and Cranbourne. Melbourne Gardens was founded in 1846 when land was reserved on the south side of the Yarra River for a new botanic garden. It extends across 38 hectares (94 acres) that slope to the river with trees, garden beds, lakes and lawns. It displays almost 50,000 individual plants representing 8,500 different species. These are displayed in 30 living plant collections. Royal Botanic Gardens Victoria is home to the State Botanical Collection, which is housed in the National Herbarium of Victoria. The collection, which includes 1.5 million preserved plants, algae and fungi, represents the largest herbarium collection in Australia and wider Oceania. It also includes Australia\'s most comprehensive botanical library.</string>
    <string name="treasury_gardens">Treasury Gardens</string>
    <string name="the_treasury_gardens_consist_of_5_8_hectares_14_acres_on_the_south_eastern_side_of_the_melbourne_central_business_district_east_melbourne_victoria_australia_the_gardens_are_bounded_by_wellington_parade_spring_street_treasury_place_and_by_the_fitzroy_gardens_across_lansdowne_street_to_the_west_they_form_part_of_a_network_of_city_gardens_including_fitzroy_gardens_carlton_gardens_flagstaff_gardens_and_kings_domain_the_gardens_are_listed_on_the_victorian_heritage_register_for_their_historical_archaeological_social_aesthetic_and_scientific_horticultural_importance_for_its_outstanding_nineteenth_century_design_path_layout_and_planting">The Treasury Gardens consist of 5.8 hectares (14 acres) on the south-eastern side of the Melbourne Central Business District, East Melbourne, Victoria, Australia. The gardens are bounded by Wellington Parade, Spring Street, Treasury Place, and by the Fitzroy Gardens across Lansdowne street to the west. They form part of a network of city gardens including Fitzroy Gardens, Carlton Gardens, Flagstaff Gardens and Kings Domain. The gardens are listed on the Victorian Heritage Register for their historical, archaeological, social, \'\'aesthetic and scientific (horticultural) importance for its outstanding nineteenth century design, path layout and planting\'\'.</string>
    <string name="the_block_arcade">The Block Arcade</string>
    <string name="the_block_arcade_is_a_heritage_shopping_arcade_that_forms_a_short_narrow_laneway_connecting_collins_street_to_little_collins_street_in_the_central_business_district_of_melbourne_it_is_also_connected_to_elizabeth_street_in_the_west_thus_forming_a_l_shaped_arcade_and_connecting_to_block_place_through_to_the_royal_arcade_melbourne_s_golden_mile_heritage_walk_runs_through_the_arcade_the_arcade_which_was_erected_between_1891_and_1893_was_designed_by_architect_david_c_askew_whose_brief_was_to_produce_something_similar_to_the_galleria_vittoria_in_milan_the_result_was_one_of_melbourne_s_most_richly_decorated_interior_spaces_replete_with_mosaic_tiled_flooring_glass_canopy_wrought_iron_and_carved_stone_finishings_the_exterior_fa_ade_of_the_six_storey_office_has_near_identical_facades_on_collins_and_elizabeth_streets_and_is_one_of_australia_s_best_surviving_examples_of_the_victorian_mannerist_style">The Block Arcade is a heritage shopping arcade that forms a short, narrow laneway, connecting Collins Street to Little Collins Street in the central business district of Melbourne. It is also connected to Elizabeth Street in the west, thus, forming a L-shaped arcade and connecting to Block Place through to the Royal Arcade. Melbourne\'s Golden Mile heritage walk runs through the arcade. The arcade which was erected between 1891 and 1893 was designed by architect David C. Askew whose brief was to produce something similar to the Galleria Vittoria in Milan. The result was one of Melbourne\'s most richly decorated interior spaces, replete with mosaic tiled flooring, glass canopy, wrought iron and carved stone finishings. The exterior façade of the six-storey office has near identical facades on Collins and Elizabeth Streets and is one of Australia\'s best surviving examples of the Victorian Mannerist style.</string>
    <string name="chinatown_melbourne">Chinatown Melbourne</string>
    <string name="chinatown_chinese_is_an_ethnic_enclave_in_the_central_business_district_cbd_of_melbourne_victoria_australia_centred_at_the_eastern_end_of_little_bourke_street_it_extends_between_the_corners_of_swanston_and_spring_streets_and_consists_of_numerous_laneways_alleys_and_arcades_established_in_the_1850s_during_the_victorian_gold_rush_it_is_notable_for_being_the_longest_continuous_chinese_settlement_in_the_western_world_and_the_oldest_chinatown_in_the_southern_hemisphere_melbourne_s_chinatown_has_played_an_important_role_in_establishing_the_culture_of_chinese_immigrants_in_australia_and_is_still_home_to_many_chinese_restaurants_cultural_venues_businesses_and_places_of_worship">Chinatown (Chinese: 墨爾本華埠) is an ethnic enclave in the Central Business District (CBD) of Melbourne, Victoria, Australia. Centred at the eastern end of Little Bourke Street, it extends between the corners of Swanston and Spring Streets, and consists of numerous laneways, alleys and arcades. Established in the 1850s during the Victorian gold rush, it is notable for being the longest continuous Chinese settlement in the Western World and the oldest Chinatown in the Southern Hemisphere. Melbourne\'s Chinatown has played an important role in establishing the culture of Chinese immigrants in Australia, and is still home to many Chinese restaurants, cultural venues, businesses and places of worship.</string>
    <string name="crown_casino_and_entertainment_complex">Crown Casino and Entertainment Complex</string>
    <string name="federation_square_is_a_venue_for_arts_culture_and_public_events_on_the_edge_of_the_melbourne_central_business_district_it_covers_an_area_of_3_2_ha_7_9_acres_at_the_intersection_of_flinders_and_swanston_streets_built_above_busy_railway_lines_and_across_the_road_from_flinders_street_station_it_incorporates_major_cultural_institutions_such_as_the_ian_potter_centre_australian_centre_for_the_moving_image_acmi_and_the_koorie_heritage_trust_as_well_as_cafes_and_bars_in_a_series_of_buildings_centred_around_a_large_paved_square_and_a_glass_walled_atrium_in_2006_federation_wharf_redeveloped_the_vaults_under_princes_walk_a_former_roadway_into_a_large_bar_with_extensive_outdoor_areas_on_the_yarra_riverbank_with_elevator_access_to_federation_square_several_proposals_have_been_prepared_for_the_area_known_as_federation_square_east_the_remaining_area_of_railyards_to_the_east">Federation Square is a venue for arts, culture and public events on the edge of the Melbourne central business district. It covers an area of 3.2 ha (7.9 acres) at the intersection of Flinders and Swanston Streets built above busy railway lines and across the road from Flinders Street station. It incorporates major cultural institutions such as the Ian Potter Centre, Australian Centre for the Moving Image (ACMI) and the Koorie Heritage Trust as well as cafes and bars in a series of buildings centred around a large paved square, and a glass walled atrium. In 2006, Federation Wharf redeveloped the vaults under Princes Walk (a former roadway) into a large bar, with extensive outdoor areas on the Yarra riverbank, with elevator access to Federation Square. Several proposals have been prepared for the area known as Federation Square East, the remaining area of railyards to the east.</string>
    <string name="docklands">Docklands</string>
    <string name="docklands_also_known_as_melbourne_docklands_to_differentiate_it_from_london_docklands_is_an_inner_suburb_of_melbourne_victoria_australia_2_km_1_2_mi_west_of_the_city_s_central_business_district_cbd_its_local_government_area_is_the_city_of_melbourne_at_the_2016_census_docklands_had_a_population_of_10_964_primarily_a_waterfront_area_centred_on_the_banks_of_the_yarra_river_it_is_bounded_by_wurundjeri_way_and_the_charles_grimes_bridge_to_the_east_citylink_to_the_west_and_lorimer_street_across_the_yarra_to_the_south_the_site_of_modern_day_docklands_was_originally_swamp_land_that_in_the_1880s_became_a_bustling_dock_area_as_part_of_the_port_of_melbourne_with_an_extensive_network_of_wharfs_heavy_rail_infrastructure_and_light_industry_following_the_containerisation_of_shipping_traffic_docklands_fell_into_disuse_and_by_the_1990s_was_virtually_abandoned_making_it_the_focal_point_of_melbourne_s_underground_rave_scene">Docklands (also known as Melbourne Docklands to differentiate it from London Docklands) is an inner suburb of Melbourne, Victoria, Australia, 2 km (1.2 mi) west of the city\'s Central Business District (CBD). Its local government area is the City of Melbourne. At the 2016 Census, Docklands had a population of 10,964. Primarily a waterfront area centred on the banks of the Yarra River, it is bounded by Wurundjeri Way and the Charles Grimes Bridge to the east, CityLink to the west and Lorimer Street across the Yarra to the south. The site of modern-day Docklands was originally swamp land that in the 1880s became a bustling dock area as part of the Port of Melbourne, with an extensive network of wharfs, heavy rail infrastructure and light industry. Following the containerisation of shipping traffic, Docklands fell into disuse and by the 1990s was virtually abandoned, making it the focal point of Melbourne\'s underground rave scene.</string>
    <string name="eureka_tower">Eureka Tower</string>
    <string name="eureka_tower_is_a_297_3_m_975_ft_skyscraper_located_in_the_southbank_precinct_of_melbourne_victoria_australia_construction_began_in_august_2002_and_the_exterior_was_completed_on_1_june_2006_the_plaza_was_finished_in_june_2006_and_the_building_was_officially_opened_on_11_october_2006_the_project_was_designed_by_melbourne_architectural_firm_fender_katsalidis_architects_and_was_built_by_grocon_grollo_australia_the_developer_of_the_tower_was_eureka_tower_pty_ltd_a_joint_venture_consisting_of_daniel_grollo_grocon_investor_tab_fried_and_one_of_the_tower_s_architects_nonda_katsalidis_it_was_the_world_s_tallest_residential_tower_when_measured_to_its_highest_floor_until_surpassed_by_ocean_heights_and_the_hhhr_tower_in_dubai_from_2006_to_2019_it_was_the_tallest_building_in_melbourne_until_the_topping_out_of_australia_108_it_is_currently_the_third_tallest_building_in_australia_behind_the_q1_in_queensland_and_australia_108_as_well_as_the_second_tallest_to_roof_excluding_spire_behind_the_latter_skyscraper">Eureka Tower is a 297.3 m (975 ft) skyscraper located in the Southbank precinct of Melbourne, Victoria, Australia. Construction began in August 2002 and the exterior was completed on 1 June 2006. The plaza was finished in June 2006 and the building was officially opened on 11 October 2006. The project was designed by Melbourne architectural firm Fender Katsalidis Architects and was built by Grocon (Grollo Australia). The developer of the tower was Eureka Tower Pty Ltd, a joint venture consisting of Daniel Grollo (Grocon), investor Tab Fried and one of the Tower\'s architects Nonda Katsalidis. It was the world\'s tallest residential tower when measured to its highest floor, until surpassed by Ocean Heights and the HHHR Tower in Dubai. From 2006 to 2019, it was the tallest building in Melbourne, until the topping out of Australia 108. It is currently the third tallest building in Australia, behind the Q1 in Queensland and Australia 108, as well as the second tallest to roof (excluding spire) behind the latter skyscraper.</string>
    <string name="federation_square">Federation Square</string>
    <string name="federation_square_is_a_venue_for_arts_culture_and_public_events_on_the_edge_of_the_melbourne_central_business_district_it_covers_an_area_of_3_2_hectors_7_9_acres_at_the_intersection_of_flinders_and_swanston_streets_built_above_busy_railway_lines_and_across_the_road_from_flinders_street_station_it_incorporates_major_cultural_institutions_such_as_the_ian_potter_centre_australian_centre_for_the_moving_image_acmi_and_the_koorie_heritage_trust_as_well_as_cafes_and_bars_in_a_series_of_buildings_centred_around_a_large_paved_square_and_a_glass_walled_atrium_in_2006_federation_wharf_redeveloped_the_vaults_under_princes_walk_a_former_roadway_into_a_large_bar_with_extensive_outdoor_areas_on_the_yarra_riverbank_with_elevator_access_to_federation_square_several_proposals_have_been_prepared_for_the_area_known_as_federation_square_east_the_remaining_area_of_railyards_to_the_east">Federation Square is a venue for arts, culture and public events on the edge of the Melbourne central business district. It covers an area of 3.2 hectors (7.9 acres) at the intersection of Flinders and Swanston Streets built above busy railway lines and across the road from Flinders Street station. It incorporates major cultural institutions such as the Ian Potter Centre, Australian Centre for the Moving Image (ACMI) and the Koorie Heritage Trust as well as cafes and bars in a series of buildings centred around a large paved square, and a glass walled atrium. In 2006, Federation Wharf redeveloped the vaults under Princes Walk (a former roadway) into a large bar, with extensive outdoor areas on the Yarra riverbank, with elevator access to Federation Square. Several proposals have been prepared for the area known as Federation Square East, the remaining area of railyards to the east.</string>
    <string name="flinder_s_street_railway_station">Flinder\'s Street Railway Station</string>
    <string name="flinders_street_railway_station_is_located_on_the_corner_of_flinders_and_swanston_streets_in_the_central_business_district_cbd_of_melbourne_victoria_australia_opened_in_1854_the_historic_station_serves_the_entire_metropolitan_rail_network_as_well_as_some_country_services_to_eastern_victoria_backing_onto_the_yarra_river_in_the_heart_of_the_city_the_complex_includes_platforms_and_structures_that_stretch_over_more_than_two_whole_city_blocks_from_east_of_swanston_street_nearly_to_market_street_flinders_street_is_served_by_metro_s_suburban_services_and_v_line_regional_services_to_gippsland_it_is_the_busiest_station_on_melbourne_s_metropolitan_network_with_an_average_of_77_153_daily_entries_recorded_in_the_2017_18_fiscal_year">Flinders Street railway station is located on the corner of Flinders and Swanston streets in the central business district (CBD) of Melbourne, Victoria, Australia. Opened in 1854, the historic station serves the entire metropolitan rail network, as well as some country services to eastern Victoria. Backing onto the Yarra River in the heart of the city, the complex includes platforms and structures that stretch over more than two whole city blocks, from east of Swanston Street nearly to Market Street. Flinders Street is served by Metro\'s suburban services, and V/Line regional services to Gippsland. It is the busiest station on Melbourne\'s metropolitan network, with an average of 77,153 daily entries recorded in the 2017/18 fiscal year.</string>
    <string name="hosier_lane">Hosier Lane</string>
    <string name="hosier_lane_is_a_laneway_in_the_central_business_district_cbd_of_melbourne_victoria_australia_located_on_the_cbd_s_southern_edge_it_extends_between_flinders_street_and_flinders_lane_and_opens_opposite_the_atrium_at_federation_square_since_the_late_1990s_hosier_lane_has_become_a_popular_tourist_attraction_due_to_its_street_art_hosier_lane_opened_as_a_street_art_gallery_in_1998_by_the_city_lights_initiative_the_lane_is_located_opposite_the_entrance_to_the_atrium_at_federation_square_on_flinders_st_placing_the_lane_prominent_position_in_the_city_the_lane_has_been_noted_for_the_quality_and_the_often_political_nature_of_its_art">Hosier Lane is a laneway in the central business district (CBD) of Melbourne, Victoria, Australia. Located on the CBD\'s southern edge, it extends between Flinders Street and Flinders Lane, and opens opposite the Atrium at Federation Square. Since the late 1990s, Hosier Lane has become a popular tourist attraction due to its street art. Hosier Lane opened as a Street Art Gallery in 1998 by the City Lights Initiative. The lane is located opposite the entrance to the Atrium at Federation Square on Flinders St, placing the lane prominent position in the city. The lane has been noted for the quality and the often political nature of its art.</string>
    <string name="luna_park">Luna Park</string>
    <string name="luna_park_melbourne_is_a_historic_amusement_park_located_on_the_foreshore_of_port_phillip_bay_in_st_kilda_melbourne_victoria_it_opened_on_13_december_1912_with_a_formal_opening_a_week_later_and_has_been_operating_almost_continuously_ever_since_luna_park_was_built_by_american_showmen_j_d_williams_2_together_with_the_phillips_brothers_harold_leon_and_herman_not_much_is_known_of_their_background_but_they_were_involved_in_the_building_of_picture_theatres_in_spokane_washington_and_vancouver_before_coming_to_sydney_in_1909_and_quickly_establishing_a_chain_of_luxury_cinemas_in_that_city_and_then_melbourne">Luna Park Melbourne is a historic amusement park located on the foreshore of Port Phillip Bay in St Kilda, Melbourne, Victoria. It opened on 13 December 1912, with a formal opening a week later, and has been operating almost continuously ever since. Luna Park was built by American showmen J D Williams,[2] together with the Phillips brothers Harold, Leon and Herman. Not much is known of their background, but they were involved in the building of picture theatres in Spokane, Washington and Vancouver before coming to Sydney in 1909 and quickly establishing a chain of luxury cinemas in that city and then Melbourne.</string>
    <string name="melbourne_aquarium">Melbourne Aquarium</string>
    <string name="sea_life_melbourne_aquarium_is_a_southern_ocean_and_antarctic_aquarium_in_central_melbourne_australia_it_is_located_on_the_banks_of_the_yarra_river_beside_and_under_the_flinders_street_viaduct_and_the_king_street_bridge_the_attraction_is_a_sea_life_centre_owned_by_merlin_entertainments_the_current_building_was_built_between_february_1998_and_december_1999_the_building_was_designed_by_peddle_thorp_architects_to_resemble_a_ship_moored_to_the_river_and_opened_in_january_2000_the_depth_of_the_building_however_was_designed_not_to_be_imposing_at_street_level_and_extends_7_metres_23_ft_below_the_surface_at_its_centre_is_a_world_first_2_200_000_litre_580_000_us_gal_oceanarium_in_the_round_where_the_spectators_become_the_spectacle_to_the_marine_life_swimming_around_them">Sea Life Melbourne Aquarium is a Southern Ocean and Antarctic aquarium in central Melbourne, Australia. It is located on the banks of the Yarra River beside and under the Flinders Street Viaduct and the King Street Bridge. The attraction is a Sea Life Centre owned by Merlin Entertainments. The current building was built between February 1998 and December 1999, the building was designed by Peddle Thorp architects to resemble a ship moored to the river, and opened in January 2000. The depth of the building however was designed not to be imposing at street level, and extends 7 metres (23 ft) below the surface. At its centre is a world first 2,200,000-litre (580,000 US gal) \'oceanarium in the round\' where the spectators become the spectacle to the marine life swimming around them.</string>
    <string name="melbourne_star_observation_deck">Melbourne Star Observation Deck</string>
    <string name="the_melbourne_star_previously_southern_star_is_a_giant_ferris_wheel_in_the_waterfront_city_precinct_in_the_docklands_area_of_melbourne_the_state_capital_of_victoria_australia_described_by_its_operators_as_the_southern_hemisphere_s_only_giant_observation_wheel_it_is_120_m_394_ft_tall_and_has_seven_spokes_reflecting_the_seven_pointed_star_of_the_australian_flag_it_opened_two_years_behind_schedule_in_december_2008_but_closed_40_days_later_due_to_structural_defects_and_was_subsequently_dismantled_for_major_repairs_the_wheel_itself_was_scrapped_and_replaced_but_the_original_support_structure_and_passenger_cabins_were_retained_it_was_originally_thought_that_reconstruction_might_be_completed_in_late_2010_but_repeated_delays_meant_it_did_not_reopen_until_23_december_2013">The Melbourne Star (previously Southern Star) is a giant Ferris wheel in the Waterfront City precinct in the Docklands area of Melbourne, the state capital of Victoria, Australia. Described by its operators as \'\'the Southern Hemisphere\'s only giant observation wheel\'\', it is 120 m (394 ft) tall and has seven spokes, reflecting the seven-pointed star of the Australian flag. It opened two years behind schedule in December 2008, but closed 40 days later due to structural defects, and was subsequently dismantled for major repairs. The wheel itself was scrapped and replaced, but the original support structure and passenger cabins were retained. It was originally thought that reconstruction might be completed in late 2010, but repeated delays meant it did not reopen until 23 December 2013.</string>
    <string name="melbourne_zoo">Melbourne Zoo</string>
    <string name="melbourne_zoo_is_a_zoo_in_melbourne_australia_it_is_located_within_royal_park_in_parkville_approximately_4_kilometres_2_5_mi_north_of_the_centre_of_melbourne_it_is_the_primary_zoo_serving_melbourne_the_zoo_contains_more_than_320_animal_species_from_australia_and_around_the_world_and_is_accessible_via_royal_park_station_on_the_upfield_railway_line_and_is_also_accessible_via_tram_routes_58_and_19_as_well_as_by_bicycle_on_the_capital_city_trail_bicycles_are_not_allowed_inside_the_zoo_itself_the_royal_melbourne_zoological_gardens_is_a_full_institutional_member_of_the_zoo_and_aquarium_association_zaa_and_the_world_association_of_zoos_and_aquariums_waza">Melbourne Zoo is a zoo in Melbourne, Australia. It is located within Royal Park in Parkville, approximately 4 kilometres (2.5 mi) north of the centre of Melbourne. It is the primary zoo serving Melbourne. The zoo contains more than 320 animal species from Australia and around the world, and is accessible via Royal Park station on the Upfield railway line, and is also accessible via tram routes 58 and 19, as well as by bicycle on the Capital City Trail. Bicycles are not allowed inside the zoo itself. The Royal Melbourne Zoological Gardens is a full institutional member of the Zoo and Aquarium Association (ZAA) and the World Association of Zoos and Aquariums (WAZA).</string>
    <string name="parliament_house_victoria">Parliament House Victoria</string>
    <string name="parliament_house_is_the_meeting_place_of_the_parliament_of_victoria_one_of_the_parliaments_of_the_australian_states_and_territories_located_on_spring_street_on_the_edge_of_the_hoddle_grid_the_grand_colonnaded_front_dominates_the_vista_up_bourke_street_construction_began_in_1855_and_the_first_stage_was_officially_opened_the_following_year_with_various_sections_completed_over_the_following_decades_it_has_never_been_completed_and_the_planned_dome_is_one_of_the_most_well_known_unbuilt_features_of_melbourne_between_1901_and_1927_it_served_as_the_meeting_place_of_the_parliament_of_australia_during_the_period_when_melbourne_was_the_temporary_national_capital_the_building_is_listed_on_the_victorian_heritage_register">Parliament House is the meeting place of the Parliament of Victoria, one of the parliaments of the Australian states and territories. Located on Spring Street on the edge of the Hoddle Grid, the grand colonnaded front dominates the vista up Bourke Street. Construction began in 1855, and the first stage was officially opened the following year, with various sections completed over the following decades; it has never been completed, and the planned dome is one of the most well known unbuilt features of Melbourne. Between 1901 and 1927, it served as the meeting place of the Parliament of Australia, during the period when Melbourne was the temporary national capital. The building is listed on the Victorian Heritage Register.</string>
    <string name="puffing_billy_railway">Puffing Billy Railway</string>
    <string name="the_puffing_billy_railway_is_a_2_ft_6_in_762_mm_narrow_gauge_heritage_railway_in_the_dandenong_ranges_in_melbourne_australia_the_primary_starting_point_operations_and_administration_centre_main_refreshment_room_also_selling_souvenirs_and_ticket_purchasing_are_located_at_belgrave_station_journeys_may_also_be_commenced_at_out_stations_of_which_some_have_limited_facilities_for_the_purchase_of_tickets_refreshments_and_souvenirs_tickets_may_also_be_purchased_from_the_conductor_before_boarding_the_train">The Puffing Billy Railway is a 2 ft 6 in (762 mm) narrow gauge heritage railway in the Dandenong Ranges in Melbourne, Australia. The primary starting point, operations and administration centre, main refreshment room (also selling souvenirs) and ticket purchasing are located at Belgrave station. Journeys may also be commenced at out-stations of which some have limited facilities for the purchase of tickets, refreshments and souvenirs. Tickets may also be purchased from the conductor before boarding the train.</string>
    <string name="queen_victoria_market">Queen Victoria Market</string>
    <string name="the_queen_victoria_market_also_known_colloquially_as_vic_market_or_queen_vic_is_a_major_landmark_in_the_central_business_district_cbd_of_melbourne_victoria_australia_covering_over_seven_hectares_17_acres_it_is_the_largest_open_air_market_in_the_southern_hemisphere_constructed_in_stages_from_the_1860s_and_officially_opened_in_1878_the_queen_victoria_market_is_the_last_remaining_major_market_in_the_cbd_and_along_with_prahran_market_and_south_melbourne_market_the_last_of_the_city_s_victorian_era_markets_still_operating_it_is_listed_on_both_the_victorian_heritage_register_and_the_national_heritage_list_and_is_one_of_melbourne_s_major_tourist_sites_attracting_approximately_10_million_visitors_annually">The Queen Victoria Market (also known colloquially as Vic Market or Queen Vic) is a major landmark in the central business district (CBD) of Melbourne, Victoria, Australia. Covering over seven hectares (17 acres), it is the largest open air market in the Southern Hemisphere. Constructed in stages from the 1860s and officially opened in 1878, the Queen Victoria Market is the last remaining major market in the CBD, and along with Prahran Market and South Melbourne Market, the last of the city\'s Victorian era markets still operating. It is listed on both the Victorian Heritage Register and the National Heritage List, and is one of Melbourne\'s major tourist sites, attracting approximately 10 million visitors annually.</string>
    <string name="shrine_of_remembrance">Shrine of Remembrance</string>
    <string name="the_shrine_of_remembrance_commonly_referred_to_as_the_shrine_is_a_war_memorial_in_melbourne_victoria_australia_located_in_kings_domain_on_st_kilda_road_it_was_built_to_honour_the_men_and_women_of_victoria_who_served_in_world_war_i_but_now_functions_as_a_memorial_to_all_australians_who_have_served_in_any_war_it_is_a_site_of_annual_observances_for_anzac_day_25_april_and_remembrance_day_11_november_and_is_one_of_the_largest_war_memorials_in_australia_designed_by_architects_phillip_hudson_and_james_wardrop_both_world_war_i_veterans_the_shrine_is_in_classical_style_based_on_the_tomb_of_mausolus_at_halicarnassus_and_the_parthenon_in_athens_greece">The Shrine of Remembrance (commonly referred to as The Shrine) is a war memorial in Melbourne, Victoria, Australia, located in Kings Domain on St Kilda Road. It was built to honour the men and women of Victoria who served in World War I, but now functions as a memorial to all Australians who have served in any war. It is a site of annual observances for ANZAC Day (25 April) and Remembrance Day (11 November), and is one of the largest war memorials in Australia. Designed by architects Phillip Hudson and James Wardrop, both World War I veterans, the Shrine is in classical style, based on the Tomb of Mausolus at Halicarnassus and the Parthenon in Athens, Greece.</string>
    <string name="southbank_and_arts_centre_melbourne">Southbank and Arts Centre Melbourne</string>
    <string name="arts_centre_melbourne_originally_known_as_the_victorian_arts_centre_and_briefly_called_the_arts_centre_is_a_performing_arts_centre_consisting_of_a_complex_of_theatres_and_concert_halls_in_the_melbourne_arts_precinct_located_in_the_central_melbourne_suburb_of_southbank_in_victoria_australia_it_was_designed_by_architect_roy_grounds_the_masterplan_for_the_complex_along_with_the_national_gallery_of_victoria_was_approved_in_1960_and_construction_began_in_1973_following_some_delays_the_complex_opened_in_stages_with_hamer_hall_opening_in_1982_and_the_theatres_building_opening_in_1984_arts_centre_melbourne_is_located_by_the_yarra_river_and_along_st_kilda_road_one_of_the_city_s_main_thoroughfares_and_extends_into_the_melbourne_arts_precinct">Arts Centre Melbourne, originally known as the Victorian Arts Centre and briefly called the Arts Centre, is a performing arts centre consisting of a complex of theatres and concert halls in the Melbourne Arts Precinct, located in the central Melbourne suburb of Southbank in Victoria, Australia. It was designed by architect Roy Grounds, the masterplan for the complex (along with the National Gallery of Victoria) was approved in 1960 and construction began in 1973 following some delays. The complex opened in stages, with Hamer Hall opening in 1982 and the Theatres Building opening in 1984. Arts Centre Melbourne is located by the Yarra River and along St Kilda Road, one of the city\'s main thoroughfares, and extends into the Melbourne Arts Precinct.</string>
    <string name="state_library_victoria">State Library Victoria</string>
    <string name="the_state_library_victoria_is_the_main_library_of_the_australian_state_of_victoria_located_in_melbourne_it_was_established_in_1854_as_the_melbourne_public_library_making_it_australia_s_oldest_public_library_and_one_of_the_first_free_libraries_in_the_world_it_is_also_australia_s_busiest_library_and_as_of_2018_the_fourth_most_visited_library_in_the_world_the_library_s_vast_collection_includes_over_two_million_books_and_350_000_photographs_manuscripts_maps_and_newspapers_with_a_special_focus_on_material_from_victoria_including_the_diaries_of_the_melbourne_s_founders_john_batman_and_john_pascoe_fawkner_the_folios_of_captain_james_cook_and_the_armour_of_ned_kelly_the_library_is_located_in_the_northern_centre_of_the_central_business_district_on_the_block_bounded_by_swanston_la_trobe_russell_and_little_lonsdale_streets">The State Library Victoria is the main library of the Australian state of Victoria. Located in Melbourne, it was established in 1854 as the Melbourne Public Library, making it Australia\'s oldest public library and one of the first free libraries in the world. It is also Australia\'s busiest library and, as of 2018, the fourth most-visited library in the world. The library\'s vast collection includes over two million books and 350,000 photographs, manuscripts, maps and newspapers, with a special focus on material from Victoria, including the diaries of the Melbourne\'s founders, John Batman and John Pascoe Fawkner, the folios of Captain James Cook, and the armour of Ned Kelly. The library is located in the northern centre of the central business district, on the block bounded by Swanston, La Trobe, Russell, and Little Lonsdale streets.</string>
    <string name="st_patrik_s_cathedral">St. Patrik\'s Cathedral</string>
    <string name="directions">Directions</string>
    <string name="the_cathedral_church_and_minor_basilica_of_saint_patrick_colloquially_st_patrick_s_cathedral_is_the_cathedral_church_of_the_roman_catholic_archdiocese_of_melbourne_in_victoria_australia_and_seat_of_its_archbishop_currently_peter_comensoli_in_1974_pope_paul_vi_conferred_the_title_and_dignity_of_minor_basilica_on_it_in_1986_pope_john_paul_ii_visited_the_cathedral_and_addressed_clergy_during_his_papal_visit_the_cathedral_is_built_on_a_traditional_east_west_axis_with_the_altar_at_the_eastern_end_symbolising_belief_in_the_resurrection_of_christ_the_plan_is_in_the_style_of_a_latin_cross_consisting_of_a_nave_with_side_aisles_transepts_with_side_aisles_a_sanctuary_with_seven_chapels_and_sacristies_although_its_103_6_metre_340_ft_length_is_marginally_shorter_than_that_of_st_mary_s_cathedral_sydney_st_patrick_s_has_the_distinction_of_being_both_the_tallest_and_overall_the_largest_church_building_in_australia">The Cathedral Church and Minor Basilica of Saint Patrick (colloquially St Patrick\'s Cathedral) is the cathedral church of the Roman Catholic Archdiocese of Melbourne in Victoria, Australia, and seat of its archbishop, currently Peter Comensoli. In 1974 Pope Paul VI conferred the title and dignity of minor basilica on it. In 1986 Pope John Paul II visited the cathedral and addressed clergy during his Papal Visit. The cathedral is built on a traditional east–west axis, with the altar at the eastern end, symbolising belief in the resurrection of Christ. The plan is in the style of a Latin cross, consisting of a nave with side aisles, transepts with side aisles, a sanctuary with seven chapels, and sacristies. Although its 103.6-metre (340 ft) length is marginally shorter than that of St Mary\'s Cathedral, Sydney, St Patrick\'s has the distinction of being both the tallest and, overall, the largest church building in Australia.</string>
    <string name="st_paul_s_cathedral">St. Paul\'s Cathedral</string>
    <string name="st_paul_s_cathedral_is_an_anglican_cathedral_in_melbourne_australia_it_is_the_cathedral_church_of_the_diocese_of_melbourne_and_the_seat_of_the_archbishop_of_melbourne_who_is_also_the_metropolitan_archbishop_of_the_province_of_victoria_the_cathedral_was_designed_by_the_english_gothic_revival_architect_william_butterfield_and_completed_in_1891_except_for_the_spires_which_were_built_to_a_different_design_from_1926_to_1932_it_is_one_of_melbourne_s_major_architectural_landmarks_st_paul_s_cathedral_is_in_a_prominent_location_at_the_centre_of_melbourne_on_the_eastern_corner_of_swanston_street_and_flinders_street_it_is_situated_diagonally_opposite_flinders_street_station_which_was_the_hub_of_19th_century_melbourne_and_remains_an_important_transport_centre">St Paul\'s Cathedral is an Anglican cathedral in Melbourne, Australia. It is the cathedral church of the Diocese of Melbourne and the seat of the Archbishop of Melbourne, who is also the metropolitan archbishop of the Province of Victoria. The cathedral was designed by the English Gothic Revival architect William Butterfield and completed in 1891, except for the spires which were built to a different design from 1926 to 1932. It is one of Melbourne\'s major architectural landmarks. St Paul\'s Cathedral is in a prominent location at the centre of Melbourne, on the eastern corner of Swanston Street and Flinders Street. It is situated diagonally opposite Flinders Street station, which was the hub of 19th-century Melbourne and remains an important transport centre.</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
</resources>